Porza Motorsports
Okay, so this time I'm going to challenge an actual race with my original car that I made in the last video.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm so glad it's finally here!
By the way, when you appeared on the show, did you leave any impression about the contents of this latest Holzer video?
When you appeared on the show, was there anything that impressed you about the contents of Holzer's latest work, Mirei?
I think it was mentioned that the evolution of ai is amazing.
I mean, 26,000 times per circuit...
Yes, 26,000 times.
The simulation reproduces the road, the road, the ground, the unevenness of the ground, and so on, in detail.
Even looking at it like this, it's very detailed.
Yes, you can see the three-dimensional effect in great detail.
You can also see the glossy feeling of the car body.
You can also see the luster of the car body.
It's amazing.
If I couldn't see everything from here to there, I wouldn't be able to see anything.
If I could only see the screen, I would feel as if I were really on the track.
It's true, you feel as if you are actually on the track.
I feel as if I'm actually on the track.
The realism of the video really blinds you to the importance of this road, doesn't it?
That's right, I didn't know that.
I thought car games were just about the cars looking cool.
But it's not like that.
I felt that it wasn't like that.
Was there anything that left an impression on you?
Well, I'm interested in the realistic Suzuka Circuit that I've been to.
I wonder how realistic it is.
I've seen it before.
I'm really looking forward to being able to feel like I've been there again.
It's wonderful that you put so much effort into the scenery and so on. It's wonderful that you're so particular about the scenery and all that.
Now let's try our hand at racing!
It's the Grand Prix of Ebituaries at Forza Motorsports!
Yay!
It's simple, but it's a car game, so let's see who's the fastest among the three of us!
It's a simple game, so let's see who's the fastest out of the three of us!
And you know, before we race, we're going to compete with each other to see who's the fastest.
But I think it's better to practice first.
First of all, we're going to practice, and to some extent, we're going to try to match each other's ability.
Shall we go to one race to see how good we are?
I'm off.
Okay, let's start the race.
Each of us will start the race.
The way you're doing it, it's beautiful.
The sun is shining.
It's beautiful.
Three, two, one.
My car is so cool!
Yay!
That's a lot of vibration.
That's for sure.
Let's go faster!
Yay for this!
It's hard
It's hard to turn.
What?
It's hard to turn!
This is so good!
I'm already running backwards.
I feel like this crowd is cheering me on. I'm kind of glad this crowd is cheering me on.
When you're running well, you're so smooth.
Right?
Yes, sir.
On the other hand, when you're not running well, it's like the controller doesn't really work for you.
I love it when it's not going well.
160 kilometers. 160 kilometers.
Oh, man, I wasn't doing it at all.
100.
I drove the car as fast as I could. I usually don't drive this fast.
100 miles an hour.
Oh, no, no, no!
It's so hard!
Straight line! I'm so proud of myself when I get to the straight line!
It's hard to get a straight line, but when it's a little to the left, it's not good.
It's hard... when the trajectory is off...
Oh, I hit a bump!
Boom!
Oh, no!
If you do it while fisching the brake, it's...
It's easier to turn.
That's great.
Turn the other way.
The car's a wreck.
Is it damaged?
It's going to be a real wreck.
Now that we've finished practice.
I'm going to try to predict the standings before we do the main race.
Who will be first and who will be last?
I would like you to predict where you will be placed.I would like to ask you to predict where you would place yourself.
I'm sure you have a sketchbook on hand.
Please try to write in each of them!
What should I do?
Okay, then.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Okay, then.
Let's hear your predictions.
Let's open it all at once.
Ready?
Let's start with Mirei.
First place goes to Yuno
Mayama is in second place
Third place goes to Hoshina.
Oh, you put yourself in third place?
Something's definitely wrong with Yuno.
Are you sure?
Because I'm not
I think I'm already in first place with this controller.
I think I'm going to have to practice a little bit.
I think I'm going to grab the court and get first place.
I'm probably taking a lot of time to get to this stage of practice.
It's taking me a long time to get to this stage of practice.
The editing points have been cut.
I think it's nice and tight.
I've already made a mistake just in the process of getting to the practice stage.
I've already made a mistake.
I'm sure we'll run into some kind of trouble.
Is it like that?Is Yuno such a Yuno?
Mayama is in first place.
Yuno's is Mayama, Yun's is second, and Mirei's is third.
Oh, no.
Why?
When we practiced, Mayama san started at the same stage
But she finished much earlier.
He finished more than 30 seconds early
I wonder if you were reassured by the dozens of kilometers on it
Certainly.
I thought I'd trust Yuno for the next second place
I thought I didn't want to lose 3rd place to Mirei
Maybe you'll be safe and sound.
I'm not going to let you lose by manipulating the controls.
I chose third place because I don't want to lose to you in the operation of the controls
Now drive spontaneously.
I'm Hoshina in first, Mayama in second, and Kunisaki in third
Why?
Anyway, in terms of the amount of time I spend thinking about controllers and stuff...
I think Yui's is pretty long
I'm a little worried that I might play in this race
I'm afraid that my pace will be too fast.
I put Kunihiro in third place.
I put Mirei in first place because she is the only one who knows the lap time.
Mirei is the only one who doesn't know her lap time.
In the practice stage...
She said, "Oh, I did the next operation," and didn't show me her lap time.
I thought she was abnormally fast.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's just a guess.Predictions.
I wonder if I'll ever get it right.
Yes.
Well then, let's move on to the race.
Let's get on with it.
This is where the battle begins.
It's a battle, isn't it?
Yes.
Let's start the race.
Rend.
Here we go.
Oh, here we go.
It's time!
Oh!
Three, two, one, go!
That feels good!
Oh, exhilarating!
That's great.
That's good. That's good.
It's hard to drive straight.
The first sharp turn is pretty difficult.
It's difficult.
But it's straight.
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good.
No, I want to go over Mirei a little bit.
Oh, no! We've got to get out of here.
Oh, but if you go a little too far down on the edge, you'll get rattled.
Yeah, it's hard.Yeah, it's hard.
Oh, God.
I wonder if Saya Yuno is in the back.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
It's getting worse...
No, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
The course is gone
The course has gone crazy
The curve is too steep...
Oh, the sand
Oh, the sand!
Oh, my God!
That's good. That's good.
Come on.
Oh, but it's 175 kilos.
Oh, wow.
Oh, you're putting it out there. It's a breeze.
It's the wind.
I weigh 50 kilos.
Why?
But okay, while you're at 50, I'll be closer.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're going away
Oh, but I see you, Mr. Mayama
Oh, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, no, I'm in the wind, I'm in the wind
Wind?Wind now?
It's the wind
Wind now?
It's windy now.
It is wind now.
Wind now?
Oh, here it comes. Here comes the hard one.
It's hard to make this sharp turn.
I can't go fast even if I want to.
Yes, it's hard to notice Mr. Kaze-no-Uu.
Surprisingly.
Straight ahead!
He's going 180km/h.
That's great.
Oh, there he is! Nice view.
Oh, it's a helicopter ride.
You're not fast, Mirei.
I can't see you at all, Mirei.
Where are you?
I'm near the Ferris wheel.
Oh, I can finally see the helicopter, too.
I've been in that Marshell before.
You're kidding?
Oh, my God, let's get out of here.
Oh, my God.
This is the hard part.
This curve...
Oh, it's so difficult. Oh, I've been caught in the gap. Oh, it's difficult. Oh, I've been caught in the gap.
It's better to make a gap at the corner.
I'm going to make a gap at the corner.
The course is quite long, isn't it?
I want to catch up.
There he is!
It's too close.
He's right in front of me.
I want to win! I want to win!
Yes!
That was the last one.
Yay!
Yuna got it.
She pulls out a little to the left at the last minute.
Is that possible?
Yes!
So, as you can see, the result is Mirei in first place!
Yay!
And Yuno came in second!
Well, that was like a real reaction.
I was so sorry. And last but not least, me.
Well, did anyone guess correctly? No one got it right, right? I didn't expect that.
How do you like it? How do you like it?
You have to change your driving technique when you take a corner or go straight.
It's very realistic, but it's very difficult to get a feel for it.
Yes, it is.
But I enjoyed the feeling of the ground and the atmosphere of the game, as if I was suddenly in the game.
If you do too much "cueing," you may not be able to make a good turn if you use the controller too much.
Yes, that's right.
It's because I was doing it with my eyes glued to the controller.I've been doing it with my eyes glazed over, and now....
Oh no.
I don't know if it's frustration or if I was just thinking about it.
Don't cry.
I'm about to cry. I'm just giving my impression.
Yes, it is.
Yes, it is. So, how about you, Yuna, who wants to pull out my last one?
Well, at first, I thought there was no one in front of me, and I was thinking what should I do, but as I started to run, I gradually got used to it and found Mayama-san.
Well, I was found.
That's for sure.
I got out of it.
I actually got to see the Ferris wheel.
I had seen it before, so I was very happy to see a view that I have seen before.
Since last time, you have customized the course, actually ran it, and even raced on it, how was it today? Yuno-san.
My brother likes cars and games, so that's why I want to forward this YouTube video to him.
Oh, to my brother.
I told him to watch it.
Sure.
I have never played these games. I have not laughed.
I've never played games. Even being laughed at is a lot of fun, so it must be even more fun for the girl I like.
I can't get enough of it.
I also wanted to try different kinds of tires, or even different kinds of cars, like sharp or round, to see how they would change.
I would like to try different types of cars, like sharp ones or round ones. I wanted to see how it would feel to change the type of car, like sharp or round.
What did you think, Mirei?
I think it is a dream come true for car lovers.
I think it's a dream come true for car enthusiasts.
Even those who were not interested in cars to begin with, being able to customize their own cars in this way is, in a way, like being a doll in a strange world.
Oh, yes, that's right.
So, I think this is a new way to enjoy cars, and I think that cars are more familiar to people than the Kiwai Dolls.
I hope that many people will give it a try.Hmmm...
Yes.
Yes, how was it?
Well, I don't have enough time by far. First of all, I realized that my skills were not enough at all, including the customization of this car body. When Yuno passed me at the end.
Yes.
So, I would like to get together with the three of us again, and this time, I would like to win the first place.
I want to do this.
I want to do it. That's why.
Yes, I want to do it.
So, we had two meetings.
Yes.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
You should try it.
Try it.
Yes, thank you very much.